MOHAMMAD **AYOUB**



OBJECTIVE

To obtain the job in my field of study and expertise. Coming with 4 years of electronic business and commerce experience at a University, two years of Interactive media management knowledge, strong proficiency with various social media platforms with over seven years of experience, and experience with graphic designing to help in elevating company campus dinning programs and increasing revenue and profitability.



EXPERIENCE

Web Messenger | Teleperformance (Homedepot)

AUG, 2020 - CURRENT

- Demonstrates accurate and professional customer service on time.
- Maintains a professional attitude and represents the company in a positive way.
- Demonstrates proper knowledge and use of departmental resources, policies and procedures.
- Responds to messages on the phone, chat and email queues.
- Maintains acceptable call times and email handling time, while remaining friendly and informative with all correspondences.
- Maintains productivity and quality standards.
- Actively search for solutions and identify trends for the appropriate staff, including possible solutions or suggestions
- Demonstrates the sense of urgency appropriate for client responses.

Digital Media Specialist | Mowasalat Qatar (Government Transportation Entity) JAN 2017 – JULY 2019

- Specialist to maximize the volume of inbound organic traffic from search engines/ Social platforms to a public and internal websites
- Leads and commission's primary and secondary market research, including focus groups and Online surveys, to communicate the voice of the company customer.
- Identifies opportunities for gathering and tracking customer intelligence and proactively shares insights with internal and external audiences.
- Oversees all company social media accounts management and managing all platform promotions
- Monitors and develops reports on competitor activity within social media spaces.

Customer Insights & Service Administrator | Mowasalat Qatar (Government Transportation Entity)

SEP 2015 - DECEMBER 2017

- Implements, manages and administers SharePoint by monitoring and reporting on the performance of the site. Maintaining the existing web-based applications and services. Keep the internal users up-to-date.
- Identifies opportunities for gathering and tracking customer intelligence and proactively shares insights with internal and external audiences through presentations, write-ups, and collateral and database repository

- Synthesizes and translates raw data into actionable analyses and reports.
- Builds strong partnerships and works collaboratively with business leads across the organization and franchises
- Drive the company towards the Online market using the paid campaigns

Operations Executive - Internship | Zajel Courier Services (Dubai Courts)MARCH 2015 – AUG 2015

- Ensure timely manifesting of shipments
- Regulate all operational activities in the collection centers
- Ensure proof of delivery is updated on the system
- Provides regular operations support by processing all shipments for customers.
- Ensuring all applicable rules and regulations are adhered to:
- Ensure all undelivered shipments are tracked and updated on the system
- Complies with pre-defined key performance indicator (KPIs) derived from the customer' service experience
- Ensures customers information security by adhering to strict guidelines for collecting, processing and recording information collected in the course of routine operations.



EDUCATION

Interactive Media Management – Postgraduate | Algonquin College 2019 – 2021

Facilitate effective completion of both individual and collaborative interactive media projects. Identify and apply discipline-specific practices that contribute to the local and global community through social responsibility, economic commitment and environmental stewardship. Use and evaluate best practices and tools to design and develop dynamic, rich-media content.

Electronic Business and Commerce – Bachelor's Degree | University of Petra 2008 – 2015

General understanding to the advanced technologies related to electronic business and knowledge management. Contributing in the establishment of leading projects the serves different work environments.



SKILLS

- Adaptability
- Teamwork
- Quick learner
- High WPM rate
- Computer skills

- Problem Solving
- Adobe Software Suite
- Database Management
- Internal Communication
- Performance management